[Music]
some funny so-and-so has left this
hammer here obviously i can't move it
clearly not worthy welcome to another
marvel video this is for thor love and
thunder
peering around through this thing this
is gonna be purely fun and entertainment
hope you enjoy it
and let's
summon the bifrost
[Music]
so now that this hammer's out the way
what we're actually going to do is try
and create a fictitious ice cream that
that the gods of asgard would enjoy in
one of their mighty feasts
we've got some color inspiration from
ragnarok and love and thunder as well so
we're going to do an asgardian blue fig
ice cream
swirl it together with a pastel dragon
honey ice cream with norse inspired red
gold chocolate shards
anyway
to the kitchen
[Music]
as we're already in the kitchen there
really wasn't that far to go so what
we're going to do is we're going to take
our asgardian blue figs now these kind
of look normal but let's see how blue
they actually are oh look they're they
really are quite blue
blimey really blue so we're going to
take these figs and we're going to put
them in a very mid-guardian pot over the
heat and turn it into a fig jam i should
say an asgardian fig jam that is
and we're going to stir that down and
let it bubble away
like the depths of hell
for
30 minutes plus just enough time to
retrieve meunier
so once your asgardian blue fig jam is
ready just gonna take it off the heat
and we're gonna start preparing the
second ice cream variant of pastel
dragon honey so you might be wondering
what a pastel dragon actually looks like
but it doesn't look like a dragon in
the traditional sense it looks like a
giant bee crossed with a badger and a
chicken these fly around the magical
flowers on asgard and produce their own
pollen which then they don't produce
pollen at all the flowers produce the
pollen but they produce their own honey
in these huge hives
for lack of a better word and then you
get this gorgeous honey which you can
see in the background it's a light to
blue color but you'll see some magic
here as we start making the ice cream
with it it turns green
once you've got all your ingredients in
the pan all nicely mixed up and foaming
like you can see take it off the heat
and then put it in a container this is
again a very mid-guardian container
we're using here but you know you've got
to use what you've got to hand
add in some of the finest milk and cream
that you find available this actually
comes from tom parker which is in
wiltshire i think and when that's all
combined you can put that in a fridge
now we're going to move on to the
asgardian blue fig ice cream obviously
this has cooled down somewhat so you can
strain it through a sieve into your pan
make sure you get all that blue
asgardian figgy goodness in there
and then to that pot you're going to add
your sugars
and your golden duck egg yolk into this
it produces a super luxurious depth of
flavor
and a little bit of color to it
once you've added that in mix in the
rest of your ingredients get it nice to
combine again look at the foam on this
ice cream base it's beautiful
put that in a again very mid-guardian
looking tub used there combine it with
the finest cream you have available
and then put it in your refrigerator
one thing to note is if you don't have a
refrigerator you can always hand the
mixes
to your nearest frost giant and they
will keep it nice and cool until you're
ready to churn
the final part of this mix
is the rose gold chocolate shards we
take our mid-guardian white chocolate
and heat that over some warm water and
to get it red we use the blood of our
fallen enemies
it gives a nice red tinge don't you know
once you've tempered your chocolate and
added your fallen
blood food coloring stuff you have to
ignore the study eye and taste this
might add to it you need to spread it
thinly over a non-stick base i have used
a silicone baking sheet here but you can
use whatever you have to hand once
that's ready
either let it harden itself or put it in
your refrigerator again hand it to your
nearest frost giant and we are going to
look at that crunch that you're getting
there we're going to decorate this
nicely
with some brushed gold and gold powder
let that harden off with your nearest
frost giant and then we're going to cut
that up nicely into suitable size shards
once both your ice creams are chilled
you can churn them as normal once the
first one is done put it in the
container keep it in your freezer
again a frost giant's hands would be
suitable i imagine then once your second
ice cream is churned you can combine the
two in your solo tub this decoration is
perfect very much in line
with our new movie
once you've completed loading the tub
the last thing to add is the rose gold
chocolate shards make sure they're put
all the way in the tub and a few on the
top pure for purely for decoration
because let's be honest asgard is all
about the gold
onto the eating
[Music]
there we go
let's get some of this asgardian ice
cream scooped shall we
look at that scoop's nice two different
color ice creams your pastel dragon
honey and your asgardian blue fig with
your rose gold chocolate shards it's
just white chocolate but it looks good
i've never had fig
ice cream before especially not as
guardian blue fig let's see what this
tastes like
[Music]
that's really good
the fig is
it's like an overwhelming
flavor that itself is quite subtle it
doesn't punch you in the face it's like
i think
piss off ghost
it's like
it's like a wave of fig comes through as
you're eating it and that's the dark one
the dark blue one is the fig
ice cream and then you've got the green
one which is that honey the
pastel dragon honey
it's just blue food coloring in normal
honey
no it's not
um
but honey and ice cream is really nice
because
it apart from the fact it's fructose so
it's really really sweet don't
substitute all your sugars for honey
just do you know probably half maybe and
go from there you can you can increase
it if you like but it's very difficult
to bring that sweetness down you can
always increase the sweetness as you go
but overall i'm really happy with this
it's just a fun video to go in line with
our stark raven hazelnuts and hunker
hulk of burning fudge that we've done
we've got some more of these we're going
to do in the future
got a johnny depp one coming so if
you're following the amber herd johnny
depp thing
i could only think of one ice cream
inspired by amber heard i'm a johnny
depp fan anyway
back to the ice cream
bit of fun hope you enjoyed it
next week we're going to get back to
doing something a bit more normal we are
producing our ice cream now selling it
locally so a lot of our time is
every day taking up
making ice cream for other people it's
really good
so you know we're actually going into
production
something we've wanted to do for a while
now so
thank you for all your support lots of
videos to come up lots of fun
entertaining videos like this one
hopefully you found this entertaining
thanks very much for watching don't
forget to like and subscribe and we'll
see you next time
right let's go and find that noob master
[Music]
we'll just take that instead
you